[
	{
		"answerText": "Pyrenees Mountains [or Pirineos; or Pyrénées; or Perinés; or Pirineus; or Pirenèus; or Pirinioak; or Auñamendiak][10] This mountain range runs the length of the Italian peninsula and is home to the rapidly-shrinking Calderone glacier. The small nation of San Marino is located around Monte Titano in this range.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BELLOCO |2014 | 4 | 10 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Name some European mountain ranges. [10] This mountain range divides France from Spain. The tiny nation of Andorra lies in these mountains, which run from the Bay of Biscay to the Cap de Creus.",
		"answers": [
			"Pyrenees",
			"Mountains",
			"Pirineos",
			"Pyrénées",
			"Perinés",
			"Pirineus",
			"Pirenèus",
			"Pirinioak",
			"Auñamendiak",
			"10",
			"This",
			"mountain",
			"range",
			"runs",
			"length",
			"Italian",
			"peninsula",
			"and",
			"home",
			"to",
			"rapidly-shrinking",
			"Calderone",
			"glacier",
			"The",
			"small",
			"nation",
			"San",
			"Marino",
			"located",
			"around",
			"Monte",
			"Titano",
			"in",
			"this"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Mississippi River[10] This lake in Minnesota is often cited as the source of the main length of the Mississippi River.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Masonic |2014 | 7 | 1 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10] Name this longest river in the United States. Its major tributaries include the Ohio and Missouri.",
		"answers": [
			"Mississippi",
			"River",
			"10",
			"This",
			"lake",
			"in",
			"Minnesota",
			"often",
			"cited",
			"as",
			"source",
			"main",
			"length"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Hawaii Island[10] This most populous of the Hawaiian islands is the home of Honolulu.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Masonic |2014 | 7 | 2 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10] Name this largest of James Cook's \"Sandwich Islands.\"",
		"answers": [
			"Hawaii",
			"Island",
			"10",
			"This",
			"most",
			"populous",
			"Hawaiian",
			"islands",
			"home",
			"Honolulu"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Lesser Antilles [prompt on Antilles] [10] The Lesser Antilles can be found in this sea. Europeans called islands in this sea the West Indies",
		"prompts": [
			"Antilles",
			"10",
			"The",
			"Lesser",
			"Antilles",
			"can",
			"be",
			"found",
			"in",
			"this",
			"sea",
			"Europeans",
			"called",
			"islands",
			"in",
			"this",
			"sea",
			"West",
			"Indies"
		],
		"heading": "NASAT  |2014 | 20 | 19 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: One member of this chain of islands is a lifeless rock named Redonda whose second-to-last king \"Robert the Bald\" was succeeded by \"Michael the Grey\" in 2009. For 10 points each:  [10] Redonda, which belongs to Antigua and Barbuda, is a member of the Leeward Islands, which makes up this island chain along with the Windward Islands. ",
		"answers": [
			"Lesser",
			"Antilles"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "French Indochina[10] Led by the Chakri dynasty, this country was the only Southeast Asian country to escape colonization. It lost Laos and the Malay peninsula to the French and British, respectively, and retains its monarchy today.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 01 | 13 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, name the following about Southeast Asia during the colonial period. [10] This French colony included the present-day countries of Vietnam, Laos, and Cambodia. These countries became independent in 1954, following the Geneva accords, despite French military intervention.",
		"answers": [
			"French",
			"Indochina",
			"10",
			"Led",
			"by",
			"Chakri",
			"dynasty",
			"this",
			"country",
			"was",
			"only",
			"Southeast",
			"Asian",
			"to",
			"escape",
			"colonization",
			"It",
			"lost",
			"Laos",
			"and",
			"Malay",
			"peninsula",
			"British",
			"respectively",
			"retains",
			"its",
			"monarchy",
			"today"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Nova Scotia[10] Nova Scotia is bordered to the west by this body of water, which has access to the Irving oil refinery and is located on a rift valley. St John's lies on it, and it separates most of New Brunswick from Nova Scotia.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 02 | 17 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Answer these questions about the maritime provinces, for 10 points each: [10] This province includes the traditionally-Scottish-inhabited Cape Breton Island, although its capital, Halifax, is on the mainland. French settlers from Acadia were deported from this place and it was renamed by the Brits in 1755.",
		"answers": [
			"Nova",
			"Scotia",
			"10",
			"bordered",
			"to",
			"west",
			"by",
			"this",
			"body",
			"water",
			"which",
			"has",
			"access",
			"Irving",
			"oil",
			"refinery",
			"and",
			"located",
			"rift",
			"valley",
			"St",
			"John's",
			"lies",
			"separates",
			"most",
			"New",
			"Brunswick",
			"from"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Berlin[10] To the southeast of Berlin is this capital of the state of Brandenburg that once served as the official seat of the Kaiser. A namesake declaration from this city called for Japan's unconditional surrender.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 04 | 20 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Its borough of Steglitz-Zehlendorf contains two bodies of water known as the greater and lesser Wannsees. For 10 points each: [10] Name this German capital city that contains the locality of Spandau and the Brandenburg Gate.",
		"answers": [
			"Berlin",
			"10",
			"To",
			"southeast",
			"this",
			"capital",
			"state",
			"Brandenburg",
			"that",
			"once",
			"served",
			"as",
			"official",
			"seat",
			"Kaiser",
			"A",
			"namesake",
			"declaration",
			"from",
			"city",
			"called",
			"for",
			"Japan's",
			"unconditional",
			"surrender"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Connecticut River[10] The Connecticut River passes just west of this capital city of Connecticut.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BISB |2013 | 2 | 11 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The so-called \"Great Attack\" occurred on this river during the War of 1812. For 10 points each: [10] Name this river which forms the border between New Hampshire and Vermont and reaches its terminus near Saybrook. It's the longest river in New England.",
		"answers": [
			"Connecticut",
			"River",
			"10",
			"The",
			"passes",
			"just",
			"west",
			"this",
			"capital",
			"city"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Great Bear Lake[10] The Great Bear Lake is located southwest of Nunavut in this Canadian territory. Settlements here include Inuvik and Hay River.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "GSAC |2013 | 1 | 6 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Uranium mining near this body of water has caused controversy and the town of Deline lies on its western shore. For 10 points each: [10] Name this lake, the largest located entirely within Canada.",
		"answers": [
			"Great",
			"Bear",
			"Lake",
			"10",
			"The",
			"located",
			"southwest",
			"Nunavut",
			"in",
			"this",
			"Canadian",
			"territory",
			"Settlements",
			"here",
			"include",
			"Inuvik",
			"and",
			"Hay",
			"River"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Rio de la Plata[10] Sites in this capital city on one shore of the Rio de la Plata include the Prado and Rodo Parks and the Palacio Salvo.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "GSAC |2013 | 5 | 6 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Name some things related to a river in South America, for 10 points each: [10] This estuary is formed by the confluence of the Paraná and Uruguay Rivers.",
		"answers": [
			"Rio",
			"de",
			"la",
			"Plata",
			"10",
			"Sites",
			"in",
			"this",
			"capital",
			"city",
			"one",
			"shore",
			"include",
			"Prado",
			"and",
			"Rodo",
			"Parks",
			"Palacio",
			"Salvo"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Bermuda[10] This other British Overseas territory located north of its namesake strait, is famous for its rock and monkeys, but is also a source of conflict between the UK and Spain.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "GSAC |2013 | 7 | 11 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Located 650 miles off Cape Hatteras, islands in this archipelago include Somerset Island and St. George's Island. For 10 points each: [10] Name this British Overseas Territory whose capital is Hamilton.",
		"answers": [
			"Bermuda",
			"10",
			"This",
			"other",
			"British",
			"Overseas",
			"territory",
			"located",
			"north",
			"its",
			"namesake",
			"strait",
			"famous",
			"for",
			"rock",
			"and",
			"monkeys",
			"but",
			"also",
			"source",
			"conflict",
			"between",
			"UK",
			"Spain"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Yellowstone National Park[10] This geyser in Yellowstone, named in 1870 for its predicability, erupts approximately every 91 minutes.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 1 | 10 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The Roosevelt Arch lies at this park's northern entrance. For 10 points each:  [10] Name this national park, the first in the United States.",
		"answers": [
			"Yellowstone",
			"National",
			"Park",
			"10",
			"This",
			"geyser",
			"in",
			"named",
			"1870",
			"for",
			"its",
			"predicability",
			"erupts",
			"approximately",
			"every",
			"91",
			"minutes"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "New York City[10] This river is connected to the Hudson via the Spuyten Duyvil [Spooi-ten Dooi-vil] Creek. It forms the northern boundary of Manhattan, and is crossed by Interstate 278 over the Triborough Bridge.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 10 | 17 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Although not the capital, this is the largest city in the state of the same name. For 10 points each: [10] Name this largest city of the United States, consisting of five boroughs.",
		"answers": [
			"New",
			"York",
			"City",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"connected",
			"to",
			"Hudson",
			"via",
			"Spuyten",
			"Duyvil",
			"Spooi-ten",
			"Dooi-vil",
			"Creek",
			"It",
			"forms",
			"northern",
			"boundary",
			"Manhattan",
			"and",
			"crossed",
			"by",
			"Interstate",
			"278",
			"over",
			"Triborough",
			"Bridge"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Dubai[10] In addition to The World Islands and The Universe Islands, Nakheel Properties developed these three artificial archipelagoes named Jebel Ali, Jumeirah, and Deira, which remain under construction. They are located off the coast of Dubai.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 11 | 9 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This city is home to the the tallest building in the world, the Burj Khalifa, which was formerly named after the city. For 10 points each: [10] Name this city on the Persian Gulf, one of the seven United Arab Emirates.",
		"answers": [
			"Dubai",
			"10",
			"In",
			"addition",
			"to",
			"The",
			"World",
			"Islands",
			"and",
			"Universe",
			"Nakheel",
			"Properties",
			"developed",
			"these",
			"three",
			"artificial",
			"archipelagoes",
			"named",
			"Jebel",
			"Ali",
			"Jumeirah",
			"Deira",
			"which",
			"remain",
			"under",
			"construction",
			"They",
			"are",
			"located",
			"off",
			"coast"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Vietnam War[10] The Vietnam Veterans Memorial was designed by this architect who received criticism for her Asian ethnicity. This architect also designed a Civil Rights Memorial in Montgomery, Alabama.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 11 | 19 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: A Moving Wall version of a structure honoring veterans of this war travels across the country. For 10 points each: [10] Give this war whose veterans are honored by two reflective black gabbro walls inscribed with the names of the killed-in-action and missing-in-action of this war.",
		"answers": [
			"Vietnam",
			"War",
			"10",
			"The",
			"Veterans",
			"Memorial",
			"was",
			"designed",
			"by",
			"this",
			"architect",
			"who",
			"received",
			"criticism",
			"for",
			"her",
			"Asian",
			"ethnicity",
			"This",
			"also",
			"Civil",
			"Rights",
			"in",
			"Montgomery",
			"Alabama"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Massachusetts [10] This only national park in Maine contains the Somes Sound and much of Mount Desert Island.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 12 | 6 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: New England is composed of six states. For 10 points each: [10] Name this state, with capital Boston, that is home to Harvard University.",
		"answers": [
			"Massachusetts",
			"10",
			"This",
			"only",
			"national",
			"park",
			"in",
			"Maine",
			"contains",
			"Somes",
			"Sound",
			"and",
			"much",
			"Mount",
			"Desert",
			"Island"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Vatican City or the Holy See [10] This nation, whose most populous quartier is Monte Carlo, is located in the French Riviera.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 13 | 11 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Europe is the smallest continent and is thus home to some really tiny countries. For 10 points each: [10] Name this nation, the smallest in the world. It is home to the headquarters of the Roman Catholic Church, leading to the amusing statistic of having six popes per square mile.  ",
		"answers": [
			"Vatican",
			"City",
			"Holy",
			"See",
			"10",
			"This",
			"nation",
			"whose",
			"most",
			"populous",
			"quartier",
			"Monte",
			"Carlo",
			"located",
			"in",
			"French",
			"Riviera"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Cape Horn[10] Cape Horn lies on this archipelago shared between Argentina and Chile. It's name in Spanish literally means \"land of fire.\"",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 14 | 3 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Going around this point means traversing the Drake Passage; two shortcuts are the Beagle Channel and the better known Strait of Magellan. For 10 points each: [10] Name this cape, the southern most point of South America.",
		"answers": [
			"Cape",
			"Horn",
			"10",
			"lies",
			"this",
			"archipelago",
			"shared",
			"between",
			"Argentina",
			"and",
			"Chile",
			"It's",
			"name",
			"in",
			"Spanish",
			"literally",
			"means",
			"land",
			"fire"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "France (or French Republic)[10] This peak, the highest in Europe outside of Russia, is located on the border of Rhone-Alpes and the Italian region of Aosta Valley.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 14 | 22 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This western European nation has 27 regions including Alsace, Lorraine, and Corsica. For 10 points each: [10] The Eiffel Tower is located in this country whose capital is located in a landlocked region named \"island of this nation\" when literally translated.",
		"answers": [
			"France",
			"French",
			"Republic",
			"10",
			"This",
			"peak",
			"highest",
			"in",
			"Europe",
			"outside",
			"Russia",
			"located",
			"border",
			"Rhone-Alpes",
			"and",
			"Italian",
			"region",
			"Aosta",
			"Valley"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Nile River[10] Third in length to the Nile and Congo, this West African river is the namesake of two of the countries it flows through. It was the principal river of the Mali, Ghana, and Songhay Empires.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 2 | 14 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The Aswan High Dam lies on this river. For 10 points each:  [10] Name this longest African river whose Blue and White varieties meet at Khartoum. The distinctive shape of this river's mouth on the Mediterranean is the origin of the term 'delta.'",
		"answers": [
			"Nile",
			"River",
			"10",
			"Third",
			"in",
			"length",
			"to",
			"and",
			"Congo",
			"this",
			"West",
			"African",
			"river",
			"namesake",
			"two",
			"countries",
			"flows",
			"through",
			"It",
			"was",
			"principal",
			"Mali",
			"Ghana",
			"Songhay",
			"Empires"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Berlin[10] This city is located in Germany's southeast. It is the capital of the state of Bavaria and is the home of BMW.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 3 | 2 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Germany is the most populous nation in the European Union, and many of those people happen to live in cities. Name some German cities, for 10 points each: [10] This city is the capital of Germany and was divided by a wall for much of the later half of the 20th century. ",
		"answers": [
			"Berlin",
			"10",
			"This",
			"city",
			"located",
			"in",
			"Germany's",
			"southeast",
			"It",
			"capital",
			"state",
			"Bavaria",
			"and",
			"home",
			"BMW"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Ontario[10] This province borders Ontario to the west and includes the city of Winnipeg.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 4 | 7 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Though many uninformed people believe that Canada is one of the 51 United States of America, it is in fact its own nation with its own subdivisions, provinces and territories. For 10 points each: [10] Name this province which is the largest by population and includes the cities of Toronto and Ottawa.",
		"answers": [
			"Ontario",
			"10",
			"This",
			"province",
			"borders",
			"to",
			"west",
			"and",
			"includes",
			"city",
			"Winnipeg"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "the South [accept equivalents][10] This Texas metropolitan region, an American Airlines hub, is the largest in the South.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 5 | 15 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The United States Census Bureau defines this region as all of the former Confederacy plus Kentucky, West Virginia, Delaware, and Maryland. For 10 points each: [10] Name this region of the United States sometimes referred to as Dixie.",
		"answers": [
			"the",
			"South",
			"equivalents",
			"10",
			"This",
			"Texas",
			"metropolitan",
			"region",
			"an",
			"American",
			"Airlines",
			"hub",
			"largest",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Crimean peninsula[10] This city on the Crimean peninsula was once home to the Soviet Black Sea fleet and is currently leased by the Russian navy.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 6 | 3 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This European peninsula is the homeland of its namesake Tatars who were expelled by the Stalin government. For 10 points each: [10] Name this southern Ukranian peninsula bounded by the Black Sea to the south and the Sea of Azov to the east.",
		"answers": [
			"Crimean",
			"peninsula",
			"10",
			"This",
			"city",
			"was",
			"once",
			"home",
			"to",
			"Soviet",
			"Black",
			"Sea",
			"fleet",
			"and",
			"currently",
			"leased",
			"by",
			"Russian",
			"navy"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Ieoh Ming Pei[10] Pei also designed glass pyramids for the entrance to this landmark art museum located in Paris. The Mona Lisa's eyes supposedly follow the viewer around while viewing her in this museum.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 6 | 10 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: In 2012, a long time goal of playing Tetris with the windows of this man's Green Building at MIT was achieved. For 10 points each: [10] Name this Chinese-American architect who used part of a glass pyramid in designing the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.",
		"answers": [
			"Ieoh",
			"Ming",
			"Pei",
			"10",
			"also",
			"designed",
			"glass",
			"pyramids",
			"for",
			"entrance",
			"to",
			"this",
			"landmark",
			"art",
			"museum",
			"located",
			"in",
			"Paris",
			"The",
			"Mona",
			"Lisa's",
			"eyes",
			"supposedly",
			"follow",
			"viewer",
			"around",
			"while",
			"viewing",
			"her"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Saint Petersburg[10] This city, the eastern terminus of the Trans-Siberian railway, is the largest Russian city on the Pacific Ocean.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 7 | 9 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Russia, the largest nation in the world, also has some pretty big cities. For 10 points each: [10] This city, the second largest in Russia, was formerly known as Leningrad and Petrograd and was the capital before Moscow.",
		"answers": [
			"Saint",
			"Petersburg",
			"10",
			"This",
			"city",
			"eastern",
			"terminus",
			"Trans-Siberian",
			"railway",
			"largest",
			"Russian",
			"Pacific",
			"Ocean"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Olympus Mons[10] Olympus Mons is a volcano on this red planet that is also the site of the Valles Marineris.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 8 | 8 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This feature formed during the Amazonian period. For 10 points each: [10] Name this shield volcano that was until 2011 known as the tallest mountain base-to-height in the Solar System.",
		"answers": [
			"Olympus",
			"Mons",
			"10",
			"volcano",
			"this",
			"red",
			"planet",
			"that",
			"also",
			"site",
			"Valles",
			"Marineris"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Tokyo [10] This island of Japan is home to Tokyo, Kobe, Hiroshima, and Sendai. It is the second most populous island in the world.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 8 | 11 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This city was originally known as Edo. For 10 points each:  [10] Name this capital city of Japan. ",
		"answers": [
			"Tokyo",
			"10",
			"This",
			"island",
			"Japan",
			"home",
			"to",
			"Kobe",
			"Hiroshima",
			"and",
			"Sendai",
			"It",
			"second",
			"most",
			"populous",
			"in",
			"world"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Tokyo [10] This island of Japan is home to Tokyo, Kobe, Hiroshima, and Sendai. It is the second most populous island in the world.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 8 | 11 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This city was originally known as Edo. For 10 points each:  [10] Name this capital city of Japan. ",
		"answers": [
			"Tokyo",
			"10",
			"This",
			"island",
			"Japan",
			"home",
			"to",
			"Kobe",
			"Hiroshima",
			"and",
			"Sendai",
			"It",
			"second",
			"most",
			"populous",
			"in",
			"world"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Alaska[10] This river, the longest in Alaska, originates in British Columbia and flows into the Bering Sea. A Canadian territory was named after this river.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 9 | 1 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: 1. This is the largest of the 50 United States. For 10 points each: [10] Name this home of the Brooks Range and the only state that has a shore on the Arctic Ocean. It is bordered by Canada on the east",
		"answers": [
			"Alaska",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"longest",
			"in",
			"originates",
			"British",
			"Columbia",
			"and",
			"flows",
			"into",
			"Bering",
			"Sea",
			"A",
			"Canadian",
			"territory",
			"was",
			"named",
			"after",
			"this"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Alberta[10] This river flows from Jasper National Park to a lake of the same name on Alberta's border with Saskatchewan, where it joins with the Peace River to form the Slave River. Its namesake oil sands are also located in Alberta.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2013 | 1 | 8 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10] Name this westernmost of Canada's Prairie provinces which contains cities such as Edmonton and Calgary.",
		"answers": [
			"Alberta",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"flows",
			"from",
			"Jasper",
			"National",
			"Park",
			"to",
			"lake",
			"same",
			"name",
			"Alberta's",
			"border",
			"with",
			"Saskatchewan",
			"where",
			"joins",
			"Peace",
			"River",
			"form",
			"Slave",
			"Its",
			"namesake",
			"oil",
			"sands",
			"are",
			"also",
			"located",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "lochs [accept Loch Eriboll or Loch Ness][10] Loch Eriboll is connected to the Pentland one of these inlets. The Solway one was the original western terminus of Hadrian's Wall.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "PACE |2013 | 3 | 3 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Give these Scottish geographic terms, for 10 points each: [10] Eriboll is a sea-inlet example of these features; the better-known freshwater ones include Ness, the supposed home of a legendary monster. ",
		"answers": [
			"lochs",
			"Loch",
			"Eriboll",
			"Ness",
			"10",
			"connected",
			"to",
			"Pentland",
			"one",
			"these",
			"inlets",
			"The",
			"Solway",
			"was",
			"original",
			"western",
			"terminus",
			"Hadrian's",
			"Wall"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Mount Rainier[10]  This other stratovolcano in the Cascade Range is famous for its 1980 eruption, the most destructive volcanic event in U.S. history which also formed this mountain's Crater Glacier.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round01.docx | 19 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This stratovolcano in Washington State is the most topographically prominent mountain in the contiguous United States. Its highest summit is known as Columbia Crest.",
		"answers": [
			"Mount",
			"Rainier",
			"10",
			"This",
			"other",
			"stratovolcano",
			"in",
			"Cascade",
			"Range",
			"famous",
			"for",
			"its",
			"1980",
			"eruption",
			"most",
			"destructive",
			"volcanic",
			"event",
			"U",
			"S",
			"history",
			"which",
			"also",
			"formed",
			"this",
			"mountain's",
			"Crater",
			"Glacier"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Sydney[10]  Sydney is the capital of this state of Australia, bordered to the south by Victoria and to the west by South Australia. Other cities in this state include Wollongong and Newcastle, and it contains Mount Kosciuszko.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round02.docx | 13 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this largest city of Australia that contains Warragamba Dam as well as an architecturally significant Opera House on Bennelong Point.",
		"answers": [
			"Sydney",
			"10",
			"capital",
			"this",
			"state",
			"Australia",
			"bordered",
			"to",
			"south",
			"by",
			"Victoria",
			"and",
			"west",
			"South",
			"Other",
			"cities",
			"in",
			"include",
			"Wollongong",
			"Newcastle",
			"contains",
			"Mount",
			"Kosciuszko"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Poland[10]  This capital of Poland sits on the Vistula and contains a statue of its coat of arms, a mermaid brandishing a sword, in its Old Town Market Place.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round03.docx | 15 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this European nation which houses the White Stork Synagogue in Wroclaw, the capital of Lower Silesian Voivodeship. Other cities on the Oder in this country include a town named Police.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Poland",
			"10",
			"This",
			"capital",
			"sits",
			"Vistula",
			"and",
			"contains",
			"statue",
			"its",
			"coat",
			"arms",
			"mermaid",
			"brandishing",
			"sword",
			"in",
			"Old",
			"Town",
			"Market",
			"Place"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Rio Grande [or Rio Bravo del Norte][10]  Mexico also features this long, narrow peninsula in its northwest. In this peninsula's north are the cities of Mexicali and Tijuana, while the Sierra de la Laguna range can be found in its south.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round04.docx | 16 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this river whose mouth is in Matamoros, a city in the state of Tamaulipas. It also serves as the southern border for Terrell and Maverick Counties.",
		"answers": [
			"Rio",
			"Grande",
			"Bravo",
			"del",
			"Norte",
			"10",
			"Mexico",
			"also",
			"features",
			"this",
			"long",
			"narrow",
			"peninsula",
			"in",
			"its",
			"northwest",
			"In",
			"peninsula's",
			"north",
			"are",
			"cities",
			"Mexicali",
			"and",
			"Tijuana",
			"while",
			"Sierra",
			"de",
			"la",
			"Laguna",
			"range",
			"can",
			"be",
			"found",
			"south"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Sea of Japan [or East Sea][10]  La Perouse Strait separates Sakhalin from this northernmost Japanese island famous for its Ainu population. Its city of Hakodate is the capital of Oshima Subprefecture.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round05.docx | 5 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this body of water bordered to the north by Russian coastal cities like Vladivostok and to the west by the Korean peninsula. This body contains Moneron Island owned by Sakhalin, known for its sea lions.",
		"answers": [
			"Sea",
			"Japan",
			"East",
			"10",
			"La",
			"Perouse",
			"Strait",
			"separates",
			"Sakhalin",
			"from",
			"this",
			"northernmost",
			"Japanese",
			"island",
			"famous",
			"for",
			"its",
			"Ainu",
			"population",
			"Its",
			"city",
			"Hakodate",
			"capital",
			"Oshima",
			"Subprefecture"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Antarctica[10]  This sea, one of two major Antarctic bays, is notoriously perilous, being the site of the freezing of Ernest Shackleton's ship Endurance. Its namesake seal can be found on the Antarctic Peninsula.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round06.docx | 6 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this continent, the windiest and driest continent on average, which has its highest point at Vinson Massif in the Ellsworth Mountains.",
		"answers": [
			"Antarctica",
			"10",
			"This",
			"sea",
			"one",
			"two",
			"major",
			"Antarctic",
			"bays"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Seattle[10]  Seattle, as well as Tacoma and Kitsap Peninsula, is located on this body of water. Admiralty Inlet connects this body of water to the Strait of Juan de Fuca, which opens into the Pacific Ocean.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round07.docx | 14 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this large coastal city in Washington State whose Century 21 Exposition in 1962 saw the construction of the Space Needle, which is a short walk from the Experience Music Project.",
		"answers": [
			"Seattle",
			"10",
			"as",
			"well",
			"Tacoma",
			"and",
			"Kitsap",
			"Peninsula",
			"located",
			"this",
			"body",
			"water",
			"Admiralty",
			"Inlet",
			"connects",
			"to",
			"Strait",
			"Juan",
			"de",
			"Fuca",
			"which",
			"opens",
			"into",
			"Pacific",
			"Ocean"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Niagara Falls[10]  This highest uninterrupted waterfall is located in Canaima National Park in Venezuela. It is named for the American aviator who discovered it upon crashing his monoplane onto Auyantepui.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round08.docx | 1 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  These falls actually consist of three waterfalls, two in New York State and Horseshoe Falls in Ontario, Canada. Its namesake river connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie.",
		"answers": [
			"Niagara",
			"Falls",
			"10",
			"This",
			"highest",
			"uninterrupted",
			"waterfall",
			"located",
			"in",
			"Canaima",
			"National",
			"Park",
			"Venezuela",
			"It",
			"named",
			"for",
			"American",
			"aviator",
			"who",
			"discovered",
			"upon",
			"crashing",
			"his",
			"monoplane",
			"onto",
			"Auyantepui"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of South Africa[10]  In South Africa's north is this desert, which primarily covers Botswana and Namibia. The Okavango River flows through this desert, home to the Dragon's Breath Cave, which contains a huge underground lake.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round09.docx | 11 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this country whose highest point, Mafadi, is located in the Drakensberg range. This polity recognizes distinct executive, judicial, and legislative capital cities.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"South",
			"Africa",
			"10",
			"In",
			"Africa's",
			"north",
			"this",
			"desert",
			"which",
			"primarily",
			"covers",
			"Botswana",
			"and",
			"Namibia",
			"The",
			"Okavango",
			"River",
			"flows",
			"through",
			"home",
			"to",
			"Dragon's",
			"Breath",
			"Cave",
			"contains",
			"huge",
			"underground",
			"lake"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Madagascar[10]  This archipelago owned by Chile and Argentina is separated from the rest of South America by the Strait of Magellan. Its southernmost island is Cape Horn, and it also includes a Staten Island.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round10.docx | 16 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This Indian Ocean island nation is located off the southeastern coast of Africa. Its capital of Antananarivo is located in the Analamanga region.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Madagascar",
			"10",
			"This",
			"archipelago",
			"owned",
			"by",
			"Chile",
			"and",
			"Argentina",
			"separated",
			"from",
			"rest",
			"South",
			"America",
			"Strait",
			"Magellan",
			"Its",
			"southernmost",
			"island",
			"Cape",
			"Horn",
			"also",
			"includes",
			"Staten",
			"Island"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Yangtze River [or Chang Jiang][10]  This structure built on the Yangtze River is the largest hydroelectric power station in the world. Completed in 2012, this controversial dam is located in Yichang, in the Hubei province.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round11.docx | 19 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This river begins at a glacier on Geladandong Peak before flowing east. One of its headwaters, the Golden Sands River, features the very deep Tiger Leaping Gorge.",
		"answers": [
			"Yangtze",
			"River",
			"Chang",
			"Jiang",
			"10",
			"This",
			"structure",
			"built",
			"largest",
			"hydroelectric",
			"power",
			"station",
			"in",
			"world",
			"Completed",
			"2012",
			"this",
			"controversial",
			"dam",
			"located",
			"Yichang",
			"Hubei",
			"province"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Andes Mountains[10]  The Andes pass through this country with both a constitutional capital and a departmental capital, which is the highest capital city in the world. This landlocked nation contains Santa Cruz and much of the Altiplano.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round12.docx | 1 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this South American mountain range, which reaches as far north as Merida in Venezuela to Mount Aconcagua in Argentina.",
		"answers": [
			"Andes",
			"Mountains",
			"10",
			"The",
			"pass",
			"through",
			"this",
			"country",
			"with",
			"both",
			"constitutional",
			"capital",
			"and",
			"departmental",
			"which",
			"highest",
			"city",
			"in",
			"world",
			"This",
			"landlocked",
			"nation",
			"contains",
			"Santa",
			"Cruz",
			"much",
			"Altiplano"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Zambezi River[10]  The Zambezi flows through the eastern portion of this nation whose capital is Luanda. This former Portuguese colony now has a province named Zaire, which borders the Democratic Republic of the Congo.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round13.docx | 20 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  The Kabompo and Lungwebungu Rivers are major tributaries of this river. It also flows along the eastern border of Namibia and the northern border of Botswana after originating in Zambia.",
		"answers": [
			"Zambezi",
			"River",
			"10",
			"The",
			"flows",
			"through",
			"eastern",
			"portion",
			"this",
			"nation",
			"whose",
			"capital",
			"Luanda",
			"This",
			"former",
			"Portuguese",
			"colony",
			"now",
			"has",
			"province",
			"named",
			"Zaire",
			"which",
			"borders",
			"Democratic",
			"Republic",
			"Congo"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Naples [or Napoli][10]  We got on a cruise ship and began sailing due west, ending up in this sea on the Mediterranean. This sea is connected to the Ligurian Sea by the Corsica Channel.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round14.docx | 8 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  We begin in this \"new city\" sandwiched between the Phlegraean Fields and Mount Vesuvius, the capital of the region of Campania. It's essential to visit the Palace of Caserta and the huge square, Piazza del Plebiscito.",
		"answers": [
			"Naples",
			"Napoli",
			"10",
			"We",
			"got",
			"cruise",
			"ship",
			"and",
			"began",
			"sailing",
			"due",
			"west",
			"ending",
			"up",
			"in",
			"this",
			"sea",
			"Mediterranean",
			"This",
			"connected",
			"to",
			"Ligurian",
			"Sea",
			"by",
			"Corsica",
			"Channel"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Guatemala[10]  This mountain range dividing Europe and Asia lies west of Yekaterinburg. It begins at the Kara Sea and ends at the Kazakh Steppes. Its highest point is Mount Narodnaya.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round15.docx | 14 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Along with Belize, this country is the border between North America and South America. Hurricanes Mitch and Stan occurred here, and its cities include Petapa, Mixco, and Villa Nueva.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Guatemala",
			"10",
			"This",
			"mountain",
			"range",
			"dividing",
			"Europe",
			"and",
			"Asia",
			"lies",
			"west",
			"Yekaterinburg",
			"It",
			"begins",
			"at",
			"Kara",
			"Sea",
			"ends",
			"Kazakh",
			"Steppes",
			"Its",
			"highest",
			"point",
			"Mount",
			"Narodnaya"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Alberta[10]  This river flows from Jasper National Park to a lake of the same name on Alberta's border with Saskatchewan, where it joins with the Peace River to form the Slave River. Its namesake oil sands are also located in Alberta.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round01.docx | 8 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this westernmost of Canada's Prairie provinces which contains cities such as Edmonton and Calgary.",
		"answers": [
			"Alberta",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"flows",
			"from",
			"Jasper",
			"National",
			"Park",
			"to",
			"lake",
			"same",
			"name",
			"Alberta's",
			"border",
			"with",
			"Saskatchewan",
			"where",
			"joins",
			"Peace",
			"River",
			"form",
			"Slave",
			"Its",
			"namesake",
			"oil",
			"sands",
			"are",
			"also",
			"located",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Idaho[10]  This river rises in Yellowstone National Park and receives the Salmon and Clearwater Rivers in Idaho before passing into Washington and eventually flowing into the Columbia River.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round02.docx | 1 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this state which contains cities such as Pocatello, Coeur d'Alene (\"KORR duh-LAYN\"), and Boise.",
		"answers": [
			"Idaho",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"rises",
			"in",
			"Yellowstone",
			"National",
			"Park",
			"and",
			"receives",
			"Salmon",
			"Clearwater",
			"Rivers",
			"passing",
			"into",
			"Washington",
			"eventually",
			"flowing",
			"Columbia",
			"River"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Kingdom of Spain (or Reino de Espana)[10]  This longest river on the Iberian Peninsula rises in the Meseta Central and flows past Toledo before emptying into the Atlantic at Lisbon.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round03.docx | 17 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this country with cities such as Cadiz, Asturias, and Valladolid which lies across the Strait of Gibraltar from Morocco.",
		"answers": [
			"Kingdom",
			"Spain",
			"Reino",
			"de",
			"Espana",
			"10",
			"This",
			"longest",
			"river",
			"Iberian",
			"Peninsula",
			"rises",
			"in",
			"Meseta",
			"Central",
			"and",
			"flows",
			"past",
			"Toledo",
			"emptying",
			"into",
			"Atlantic",
			"at",
			"Lisbon"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Borneo[10]  Indonesia also contains this island that contains the cities of Banda Aceh, Palembang, and Medan. It lies across the Sunda Strait from Java and across the Strait of Malacca from the Malay Peninsula.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round04.docx | 17 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this third largest island in the world, which is shared between Brunei, Malaysia, and Indonesia.",
		"answers": [
			"Borneo",
			"10",
			"Indonesia",
			"also",
			"contains",
			"this",
			"island",
			"that",
			"cities",
			"Banda",
			"Aceh",
			"Palembang",
			"and",
			"Medan",
			"It",
			"lies",
			"across",
			"Sunda",
			"Strait",
			"from",
			"Java",
			"Malacca",
			"Malay",
			"Peninsula"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Namibia[10]  This desert, home to the Bushmen and the Makgadikgadi salt pan, is shared among Namibia, South Africa, and Botswana.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round05.docx | 3 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this country which contains Walvis Bay and the Skeleton Coast with capital at Windhoek. Its southern border is formed by the Orange River.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Namibia",
			"10",
			"This",
			"desert",
			"home",
			"to",
			"Bushmen",
			"and",
			"Makgadikgadi",
			"salt",
			"pan",
			"shared",
			"among",
			"South",
			"Africa",
			"Botswana"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "New Mexico[10]  This national park lies in southeastern New Mexico and features the Big Room, the third largest cave chamber in North America.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round06.docx | 20 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this state bisected by the Rio Grande which contains White Sands National Monument and cities like Alamogordo, Las Cruces, Albuquerque, and Santa Fe.",
		"answers": [
			"New",
			"Mexico",
			"10",
			"This",
			"national",
			"park",
			"lies",
			"in",
			"southeastern",
			"and",
			"features",
			"Big",
			"Room",
			"third",
			"largest",
			"cave",
			"chamber",
			"North",
			"America"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Munich (or Munchen)[10]  Before joining the Danube at Belgrade, the Sava flows through the capital of this country that contains the Istrian Peninsula and the cities of Rijeka and Dubrovnik.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round07.docx | 7 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Before joining the Danube, the Isar flows through this Oktoberfest-celebrating capital city of Bavaria.",
		"answers": [
			"Munich",
			"Munchen",
			"10",
			"Before",
			"joining",
			"Danube",
			"at",
			"Belgrade",
			"Sava",
			"flows",
			"through",
			"capital",
			"this",
			"country",
			"that",
			"contains",
			"Istrian",
			"Peninsula",
			"and",
			"cities",
			"Rijeka",
			"Dubrovnik"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Nicaragua[10]  This country contains the Great Blue Hole as well as a namesake barrier reef that is the second longest in the world. It is the only officially English-speaking country in Central America and the only one not to border the Pacific Ocean.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round08.docx | 11 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This country that lies at the southern end of the Gulf of Fonseca and contains the largest lake in Central America as well as a lake named after its capital, Managua.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Nicaragua",
			"10",
			"This",
			"country",
			"contains",
			"Great",
			"Blue",
			"Hole",
			"as",
			"well",
			"namesake",
			"barrier",
			"reef",
			"that",
			"second",
			"longest",
			"in",
			"world",
			"It",
			"only",
			"officially",
			"English-speaking",
			"Central",
			"America",
			"and",
			"one"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Toronto[10]  Queen Charlotte Island is a part of this Canadian province, which also features the Fraser River and the Hecate Strait. Its capital is Victoria and its largest city lies across the border from the state of Washington.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round09.docx | 7 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This provincial capital of Ontario lies on Lake Ontario. The most recognizable feature of this largest city in Canada is its 1800-foot tall CN Tower.",
		"answers": [
			"Toronto",
			"10",
			"Queen",
			"Charlotte",
			"Island",
			"part",
			"this",
			"Canadian",
			"province",
			"which",
			"also",
			"features",
			"Fraser",
			"River",
			"and",
			"Hecate",
			"Strait",
			"Its",
			"capital",
			"Victoria",
			"its",
			"largest",
			"city",
			"lies",
			"across",
			"border",
			"from",
			"state",
			"Washington"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Minnesota[10]  This river forms the border between Minnesota and North Dakota. Another river of the same name forms the border between Oklahoma and Texas and flows into the Mississippi River in Louisiana.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round10.docx | 1 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this state which contains Lake Itasca as well as the cities of Duluth, St. Paul, and Minneapolis.",
		"answers": [
			"Minnesota",
			"10",
			"This",
			"river",
			"forms",
			"border",
			"between",
			"and",
			"North",
			"Dakota"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Santiago (accept but do not reveal Santiago de Chile)[10]  Santiago is the capital of this long, narrow country which contains the western half of Tierra del Fuego in its south and the Atacama Desert in its north.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round11.docx | 8 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this South American capital city which lies 60 miles southwest of Aconcagua and 70 miles southeast of the port of Valparaiso.",
		"answers": [
			"Santiago",
			"but"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Scotland (or Alba)[10]  Scotland controls the Shetland Islands, the Orkney Islands, and this archipelago lying off the western coast of Scotland which contains the Isle of Lewis and the Isle of Skye.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round12.docx | 21 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this country which contains the Firth of Forth and the Firth of Clyde as well as cities such as Aberdeen, Glasgow, and its capital Edinburgh, which lies north of England.",
		"answers": [
			"Scotland",
			"Alba",
			"10",
			"controls",
			"Shetland",
			"Islands",
			"Orkney",
			"and",
			"this",
			"archipelago",
			"lying",
			"off",
			"western",
			"coast",
			"which",
			"contains",
			"Isle",
			"Lewis",
			"Skye"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "New Guinea (or Papua Island; do not accept \"Papua New Guinea\")[10]  This strait, which connects the Arafura Sea to the Coral Sea, separates New Guinea from the Cape York Peninsula.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round13.docx | 11 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this large island, the western portion of which contains Puncak Jaya and is controlled by Indonesia, and the eastern portion of which contains a namesake country with capital at Port Moresby.",
		"answers": [
			"New",
			"Guinea",
			"Papua",
			"Island"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Nevada[10]  New Orleans lies in between the Mississippi River and this second largest saltwater lake in the United States.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round14.docx | 18 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Lake Tahoe lies on the border between California and this state, which also contains Pyramid Lake and cities such as Reno and Carson City.",
		"answers": [
			"Nevada",
			"10",
			"New",
			"Orleans",
			"lies",
			"in",
			"between",
			"Mississippi",
			"River",
			"and",
			"this",
			"second",
			"largest",
			"saltwater",
			"lake",
			"United",
			"States"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Islamic Republic of Afghanistan[10]  Tirich Mir is the highest point in this mountain range which dominates central and northeastern Afghanistan.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round15.docx | 11 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this landlocked country in which the Helmand River drains into the Sistan Basin. Its cities include Herat, Kandahar, and its capital, Kabul.",
		"answers": [
			"Islamic",
			"Republic",
			"Afghanistan",
			"10",
			"Tirich",
			"Mir",
			"highest",
			"point",
			"in",
			"this",
			"mountain",
			"range",
			"which",
			"dominates",
			"central",
			"and",
			"northeastern"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Republic of Djibouti[10]  The Bab-el-Mandeb connects the Gulf of Aden to this sea, which is in turn connected to the Mediterranean Sea by the Suez Canal.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round16.docx | 19 | Geography |  | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this small country that lies across the Bab-el-Mandeb from Yemen.",
		"answers": [
			"Republic",
			"Djibouti",
			"10",
			"The",
			"Bab-el-Mandeb",
			"connects",
			"Gulf",
			"Aden",
			"to",
			"this",
			"sea",
			"which",
			"in",
			"turn",
			"connected",
			"Mediterranean",
			"Sea",
			"by",
			"Suez",
			"Canal"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Johannesburg [or Egoli][10] This city near Johannesburg is the administrative capital of South Africa, as opposed to the other two judicial  and legislative capitals. It is named after a leader of the Voortrekkers.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2012 | 4 | 2 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: It is the world's largest city not located on a river or body of water. For 10 points each: [10] Name this city containing the impoverished Soweto area; it is the largest city in South Africa.",
		"answers": [
			"Johannesburg",
			"Egoli",
			"10",
			"This",
			"city",
			"near",
			"administrative",
			"capital",
			"South",
			"Africa",
			"as",
			"opposed",
			"to",
			"other",
			"two",
			"judicial",
			"and",
			"legislative",
			"capitals",
			"It",
			"named",
			"after",
			"leader",
			"Voortrekkers"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Anchorage[10] This western Alaskan city was a gold mining boom town, and is the end point of the Iditarod Trail Sled Dog Race.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BHSAT |2011 | 1 | 16 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: America's largest state is also one of its least populated. For 10 points each: [10] This is Alaska's largest city, home to over half its population.",
		"answers": [
			"Anchorage",
			"10",
			"This",
			"western",
			"Alaskan",
			"city",
			"was",
			"gold",
			"mining",
			"boom",
			"town",
			"and",
			"end",
			"point",
			"Iditarod",
			"Trail",
			"Sled",
			"Dog",
			"Race"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Philippines[10] This city adjacent to the capital Manila is the largest city in the Philippines.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BHSAT |2011 | 2 | 5 | Geography | None | HS",
		"subject": "Geography",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Consisting of over 7,000 islands, this country featured a large settlement on a mountainous landfill in Payatas.. For 10 points each: [10] Name this country, separated from Taiwan by the Luzon Strait and from Indonesia by the Sulu Sea. Its capital city is Manila.",
		"answers": [
			"Philippines",
			"10",
			"This",
			"city",
			"adjacent",
			"to",
			"capital",
			"Manila",
			"largest",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Breaking Bad[10]  Using his knowledge of chemistry, Walter is able to produce a 99.1% pure form of methamphetamine that is this color because of his usage of methylamine instead of pseudoephedrine.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 01 | 12 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: A spin-off of this AMC TV series, Better Call Saul, is set to be produced. For 10 points each: [10] Name this TV show that documents the escapades of terminal cancer patient Walter White as he struggles to provide for his family through the dealing of methamphetamine.",
		"answers": [
			"Breaking",
			"Bad",
			"10",
			"Using",
			"his",
			"knowledge",
			"chemistry",
			"Walter",
			"able",
			"to",
			"produce",
			"99",
			"1%",
			"pure",
			"form",
			"methamphetamine",
			"that",
			"this",
			"color",
			"because",
			"usage",
			"methylamine",
			"instead",
			"pseudoephedrine"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Wicked[10] This lead singer in the Broadway production of Wicked performed as the green-faced witch Elphaba in \"Defying Gravity.\" John Travolta infamously mispronounced her name at the 2014 Academy Awards.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 02 | 9 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: In this musical, Prince Fiyero advises his fellow students that they should stop studying and live the \"unexamined life\". For 10 points each: [10] Name this 2003 musical with the number \"Dancing Through Life\", in which Fiyero wins the admiration of many female students, including a girl whom Boq asks to a dance. She convinces Boq to ask Nessarose instead.",
		"answers": [
			"Wicked",
			"10",
			"This",
			"lead",
			"singer",
			"in",
			"Broadway",
			"production",
			"performed",
			"as",
			"green-faced",
			"witch",
			"Elphaba",
			"Defying",
			"Gravity",
			"John",
			"Travolta",
			"infamously",
			"mispronounced",
			"her",
			"name",
			"at",
			"2014",
			"Academy",
			"Awards"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Yankee Stadium[10] This stadium located in the Bronx, New York was dubbed \"The House that Ruth Built\" due to Babe Ruth's many impressive games played in it. It takes its name from its home team.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 03 | 11 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, name these cathedrals of America's pastime: baseball stadiums. [10] This stadium located in the Bronx, New York was dubbed \"The House that Ruth Built\" due to Babe Ruth's many impressive games played in it. It takes its name from its home team.",
		"answers": [
			"Yankee",
			"Stadium",
			"10",
			"This",
			"stadium",
			"located",
			"in",
			"Bronx",
			"New",
			"York",
			"was",
			"dubbed",
			"The",
			"House",
			"that",
			"Ruth",
			"Built",
			"due",
			"to",
			"Babe",
			"Ruth's",
			"many",
			"impressive",
			"games",
			"played",
			"It",
			"takes",
			"its",
			"name",
			"from",
			"home",
			"team"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "\"Rap God\"[10] Rap God was a song by this rapper, who occasionally performs under his alter-ego, Slim Shady. Singles from his 2010 album Recovery include \"Lose Yourself\" and \"Love the Way You Lie,\" which features Rihanna.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 05 | 4 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The artist of this song was going to go easy on us not to hurt our feelings, but changes his mind after he realizes that he's only going to get this one chance. For 10 points each: [10] Name this song in which the artist spews out a long string of unintelligible jibber-jabber before declaring that he's beginning to feel like the title figure.",
		"answers": [
			"Rap",
			"God",
			"10",
			"was",
			"song",
			"by",
			"this",
			"rapper",
			"who",
			"occasionally",
			"performs",
			"under",
			"his",
			"alter-ego",
			"Slim",
			"Shady",
			"Singles",
			"from",
			"2010",
			"album",
			"Recovery",
			"include",
			"Lose",
			"Yourself",
			"and",
			"Love",
			"Way",
			"You",
			"Lie",
			"which",
			"features",
			"Rihanna"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "zombies [accept equivalents like the undead][10] This video game follows Joel and Ellie, who fight Cordyceps-infected zombies as they traverse a post-apocalyptic landscape to find the Fireflies.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 06 | 1 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: John Marston fights these beings in a Red Dead Redemption downloadable pack. For 10 points each: [10] Name these beings who drop rotten flesh in Minecraft and name a special mode in the Call of Duty series. They are the principal enemies in Left 4 Dead, Resident Evil, and The Walking Dead. ",
		"answers": [
			"zombies",
			"equivalents",
			"undead",
			"10",
			"This",
			"video",
			"game",
			"follows",
			"Joel",
			"and",
			"Ellie",
			"who",
			"fight",
			"Cordyceps-infected",
			"as",
			"they",
			"traverse",
			"post-apocalyptic",
			"landscape",
			"to",
			"find",
			"Fireflies"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Sigur Rós (\"see-uhr rose\")[10] Sigur Rós collaborated with this English band on Merce Cunningham's Split Sides. Headed by Thom Yorke, they released the song \"Creep\" and the albums Kid A, OK Computer, and In Rainbows.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 07 | 6 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This band exhibited a more aggressive metal sound in their recent album Kveikur. For 10 points each: [10] Name this post-rock band led by Jonsi, who plays bowed guitar and sings ethereal vocals in Vonlenska. Their albums include Agaetis byrjun (\"OW-guy-tis bee-ARR-yun\"), Takk, and Valtari. ",
		"answers": [
			"Sigur",
			"Rós",
			"see-uhr",
			"rose",
			"10",
			"collaborated",
			"with",
			"this",
			"English",
			"band",
			"Merce",
			"Cunningham's",
			"Split",
			"Sides",
			"Headed",
			"by",
			"Thom",
			"Yorke",
			"they",
			"released",
			"song",
			"Creep",
			"and",
			"albums",
			"Kid",
			"A",
			"OK",
			"Computer",
			"In",
			"Rainbows"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Little Prince[10] This author of The Little Prince and Southern Mail expanded on his experience as a stranded aviator in the Sahara Desert in his memoir Wind, Sand, and Stars.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2014 | 07 | 21 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Its narrator begins by recalling his childhood sketch of a boa constrictor devouring an elephant. For 10 points each: [10] Identify this novel in which a wandering boy who leaves the asteroid B-612 because he does not know how to love his rose. He meets the narrator, now a full-fledged pilot whose plane has broken down in the Sahara.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Little",
			"Prince",
			"10",
			"This",
			"author",
			"and",
			"Southern",
			"Mail",
			"expanded",
			"his",
			"experience",
			"as",
			"stranded",
			"aviator",
			"in",
			"Sahara",
			"Desert",
			"memoir",
			"Wind",
			"Sand",
			"Stars"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Lorde (accept Ella Yelich-O'Connor)[10] That single by Lorde is this song that advocates against lavish lifestyles in its chorus: \"that kind of luxe just ain't for us / we crave a different kind of buzz.\"",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "GSAC |2013 | 4 | 3 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The chorus of one song by this artist begins \"Baby be the class clown/ I'll be the beauty queen in tears.\" For 10 points each: [10] Name this sixteen-year-old artist from New Zealand, whose singles include \"Tennis Court\" and one that begins \"I've never seen a diamond in the flesh.\"",
		"answers": [
			"Lorde",
			"Ella",
			"Yelich-O'Connor",
			"10",
			"That",
			"single",
			"by",
			"this",
			"song",
			"that",
			"advocates",
			"against",
			"lavish",
			"lifestyles",
			"in",
			"its",
			"chorus:",
			"luxe",
			"just",
			"ain't",
			"for",
			"us",
			"/",
			"we",
			"crave",
			"different",
			"buzz"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "New Orleans Saints [accept either][10] This tight end for the Saints played basketball in college. In 2011, he broke the receiving yards record for a tight end, only to have his record broken later that day by Rob Gronkowski.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "GSAC |2013 | 6 | 9 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Sean Payton is the coach for this NFC South team led by quarterback Drew Brees. For 10 points each: [10] Name this team that plays in the Mercedes-Benz Superdome and is known for their fans' expression, \"Who Dat?\"",
		"answers": [
			"New",
			"Orleans",
			"Saints",
			"10",
			"This",
			"tight",
			"end",
			"for",
			"played",
			"basketball",
			"in",
			"college",
			"In",
			"2011",
			"he",
			"broke",
			"receiving",
			"yards",
			"record",
			"only",
			"to",
			"have",
			"his",
			"broken",
			"later",
			"that",
			"day",
			"by",
			"Rob",
			"Gronkowski"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Hushpuppy[10] Hushpuppy is the main character of this Benh Zeitlin film set on a Louisiana island devastated by a hurricane. Zeitlin and Wallis received Academy Award nominations for their work in this film.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 10 | 10 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This character listens to her father's last heartbeat after negotiating a peace with the Aurochs. For 10 points each: [10] Name this protagonist of a 2012 indie film played by Quvenzhane Wallis who lives in \"The Bathtub\" with her father Wink.",
		"answers": [
			"Hushpuppy",
			"10",
			"main",
			"character",
			"this",
			"Benh",
			"Zeitlin",
			"film",
			"set",
			"Louisiana",
			"island",
			"devastated",
			"by",
			"hurricane",
			"and",
			"Wallis",
			"received",
			"Academy",
			"Award",
			"nominations",
			"for",
			"their",
			"work",
			"in"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Duke Nukem Forever[10] After Episode 2 of the second installment in this series came out, the lack of any information about the next installment featuring Gordon Freeman helped lead to a joke that Valve can't count to three.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 12 | 16 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, name these video games we've been waiting a long time for: [10] This title became for a long time the most infamous example of vaporware, with its previous \"3D\" installation coming out in 1996. It was finally released in 2011, allowing its muscle-toting, bubblegum chewing action figure to see the light of day once again.",
		"answers": [
			"Duke",
			"Nukem",
			"Forever",
			"10",
			"After",
			"Episode",
			"2",
			"second",
			"installment",
			"in",
			"this",
			"series",
			"came",
			"out",
			"lack",
			"information",
			"about",
			"next",
			"featuring",
			"Gordon",
			"Freeman",
			"helped",
			"lead",
			"to",
			"joke",
			"that",
			"Valve",
			"can't",
			"count",
			"three"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "House of Cards[10] House of Cards airs exclusively on this online streaming site, that controversially split its rental and streaming services.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 14 | 7 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This show stars Kevin Spacey as House Majority Whip Frank Underwood. For 10 points each: [10] Name this online series focusing on the efforts of Underwood to undermine the government after getting denied for Secretary of State.",
		"answers": [
			"House",
			"Cards",
			"10",
			"airs",
			"exclusively",
			"this",
			"online",
			"streaming",
			"site",
			"that",
			"controversially",
			"split",
			"its",
			"rental",
			"and",
			"services"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "James Harden[10] Harden was traded to the Houston Rockets from this team, which reached the 2012 NBA Finals behind Kevin Durant and Russell Westbrook.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 2 | 18 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: This NBA player's beard has inspired multiple Facebook and Twitter accounts, for 10 points each: [10] Name this shooting guard who was drafted out of Arizona State in 2009 by his former team, but now plays alongside Jeremy Lin in Houston.",
		"answers": [
			"James",
			"Harden",
			"10",
			"was",
			"traded",
			"to",
			"Houston",
			"Rockets",
			"from",
			"this",
			"team",
			"which",
			"reached",
			"2012",
			"NBA",
			"Finals",
			"behind",
			"Kevin",
			"Durant",
			"and",
			"Russell",
			"Westbrook"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Flash[10] This third incarnation of the Flash took over after Barry Allen was killed during the Crisis on Infinite Earths. He was the nephew of Barry's wife Iris.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 4 | 16 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Incarnations of this superhero have included Jay Garrick and Barry Allen. For 10 points each: [10] Name this \"Scarlet Speedster\" from the DC Comics universe who posses super-speed and has a lightning bolt insignia.",
		"answers": [
			"Flash",
			"10",
			"This",
			"third",
			"incarnation",
			"took",
			"over",
			"after",
			"Barry",
			"Allen",
			"was",
			"killed",
			"during",
			"Crisis",
			"Infinite",
			"Earths",
			"He",
			"nephew",
			"Barry's",
			"wife",
			"Iris"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Death Cab For Cutie[10] In The Motorcycle Diaries, this character swims across the Amazon River to be with some lepers on his birthday. His visage is commonly seen on T-shirts.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 6 | 4 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, answer some questions about people who find themselves separated by bodies of water.  [10] This band's \"Transatlanticism\", about a relationship separated by the Atlantic, has a chorus of \"I need you so much closer.\" Other songs by them include \"I Will Possess Your Heart\" and \"I Will Follow You Into the Dark.\"",
		"answers": [
			"Death",
			"Cab",
			"For",
			"Cutie",
			"10",
			"In",
			"The",
			"Motorcycle",
			"Diaries",
			"this",
			"character",
			"swims",
			"across",
			"Amazon",
			"River",
			"to",
			"be",
			"with",
			"some",
			"lepers",
			"his",
			"birthday",
			"His",
			"visage",
			"commonly",
			"seen",
			"T-shirts"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Firefly[10] Centering around the exploits of the dysfunctional Bluth family, new episodes of this comedy starring Jason Bateman will start airing on Netflix in the spring of 2013, seven years after it was originally cancelled by Fox.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 8 | 1 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The Fox network has cancelled some of the best TV shows of all time. Name three of them, for 10 points each: [10] Starring Nathan Fillion and Morena Baccarin, this space western epic acquired so much post-cancellation support that its story was allowed to continue in the feature film Serenity.",
		"answers": [
			"Firefly",
			"10",
			"Centering",
			"around",
			"exploits",
			"dysfunctional",
			"Bluth",
			"family",
			"new",
			"episodes",
			"this",
			"comedy",
			"starring",
			"Jason",
			"Bateman",
			"will",
			"start",
			"airing",
			"Netflix",
			"in",
			"spring",
			"2013",
			"seven",
			"years",
			"after",
			"was",
			"originally",
			"cancelled",
			"by",
			"Fox"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Firefly[10] Centering around the exploits of the dysfunctional Bluth family, new episodes of this comedy starring Jason Bateman will start airing on Netflix in the spring of 2013, seven years after it was originally cancelled by Fox.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "James |2013 | 8 | 1 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: The Fox network has cancelled some of the best TV shows of all time. Name three of them, for 10 points each: [10] Starring Nathan Fillion and Morena Baccarin, this space western epic acquired so much post-cancellation support that its story was allowed to continue in the feature film Serenity.",
		"answers": [
			"Firefly",
			"10",
			"Centering",
			"around",
			"exploits",
			"dysfunctional",
			"Bluth",
			"family",
			"new",
			"episodes",
			"this",
			"comedy",
			"starring",
			"Jason",
			"Bateman",
			"will",
			"start",
			"airing",
			"Netflix",
			"in",
			"spring",
			"2013",
			"seven",
			"years",
			"after",
			"was",
			"originally",
			"cancelled",
			"by",
			"Fox"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Back in Black[10] Back in Black is a song by this Australian band, famous for other songs such as Shoot to Thrill and Highway to Hell.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2013 | 1 | 2 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10] Name this song, famous for its intro guitar riff, whose singer has \"hit the sack\" and is \"glad\" since he's \"been too long\".",
		"answers": [
			"Back",
			"in",
			"Black",
			"10",
			"song",
			"by",
			"this",
			"Australian",
			"band",
			"famous",
			"for",
			"other",
			"songs",
			"such",
			"as",
			"Shoot",
			"to",
			"Thrill",
			"and",
			"Highway",
			"Hell"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Kellogg's Frosted Flakes[10]  This fictional serial killer is depicted in The Silence of the Lambs. In the movie adaptation, he is played by Anthony Hopkins and claimed to have eaten a census taker's liver with \"some fava beans and a nice chianti\".",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round01.docx | 11 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This Kellogg cereal known as Zucaritas in Latin America is a good source of Vitamin D. Its namesake flattened corn pieces are coated in sugar, and Tony the Tiger insists that they are delicious.",
		"answers": [
			"Kellogg's",
			"Frosted",
			"Flakes",
			"10",
			"This",
			"fictional",
			"serial",
			"killer",
			"depicted",
			"in",
			"The",
			"Silence",
			"Lambs",
			"In",
			"movie",
			"adaptation",
			"he",
			"played",
			"by",
			"Anthony",
			"Hopkins",
			"and",
			"claimed",
			"to",
			"have",
			"eaten",
			"census",
			"taker's",
			"liver",
			"with",
			"some",
			"fava",
			"beans",
			"nice",
			"chianti"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "\"Song 2\"[10]  Blur clashed with this band whose members include the Gallagher brothers. Their songs include \"Rock 'N' Roll Star\" from Definitely Maybe and \"Wonderwall\" from [What's the Story] Morning Glory.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round02.docx | 7 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This Britpop song from Blur's self-titled album includes the lines \"I got my head checked\" and \"Pleased to meet you\". Its raucous chorus sees Damon Albarn yell \"Woo-hoo!\".",
		"answers": [
			"Song",
			"2",
			"10",
			"Blur",
			"clashed",
			"with",
			"this",
			"band",
			"whose",
			"members",
			"include",
			"Gallagher",
			"brothers",
			"Their",
			"songs",
			"Rock",
			"'N'",
			"Roll",
			"Star",
			"from",
			"Definitely",
			"Maybe",
			"and",
			"Wonderwall",
			"What's",
			"Story",
			"Morning",
			"Glory"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Mojo Jojo (\"mo-jo JO-JO!\")[10]  Mojo Jojo is the main antagonist of this animated TV show broadcast by Cartoon Network. It centers around the superhero trio of Blossom, Bubbles and Buttercup in the city of Townsville.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round03.docx | 7 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this purple-caped chimpanzee with green skin and a huge brain. He creates the Rowdyruff Boys to counter his archenemies.",
		"answers": [
			"Mojo",
			"Jojo",
			"mo-jo",
			"JO-JO!",
			"10",
			"main",
			"antagonist",
			"this",
			"animated",
			"TV",
			"show",
			"broadcast",
			"by",
			"Cartoon",
			"Network",
			"It",
			"centers",
			"around",
			"superhero",
			"trio",
			"Blossom",
			"Bubbles",
			"and",
			"Buttercup",
			"in",
			"city",
			"Townsville"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Inigo Montoya[10]  Inigo Montoya and Fezzik accompany Westley on his quest to save Buttercup in this film that notably cuts the ambiguous ending of the William Goldman novel.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round05.docx | 15 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this Spaniard who is finally able to kill Count Rugen. He does so while repeating a line in which he introduces himself and states \"You killed my father. Prepare to die.\"",
		"answers": [
			"Inigo",
			"Montoya",
			"10",
			"and",
			"Fezzik",
			"accompany",
			"Westley",
			"his",
			"quest",
			"to",
			"save",
			"Buttercup",
			"in",
			"this",
			"film",
			"that"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Marlon Brando Jr.[10]  This actor gained popularity after he appeared as the moody Cal Trask in Kazan's East of Eden. He died in a car crash a month after the release of Rebel Without a Cause, in which he played the angsty teenager Jim Stark.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round05.docx | 18 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Kazan launched the career of this actor who played Stanley Kowalski in A Streetcar Named Desire and Terry Malloy in On the Waterfront. His other roles include motorcycle gang leader Johnny Strabler and Vito Corleone.",
		"answers": [
			"Marlon",
			"Brando",
			"Jr",
			"10",
			"This",
			"actor",
			"gained",
			"popularity",
			"after",
			"he",
			"appeared",
			"as",
			"moody",
			"Cal",
			"Trask",
			"in",
			"Kazan's",
			"East",
			"Eden",
			"He",
			"died",
			"car",
			"crash",
			"month",
			"release",
			"Rebel",
			"Without",
			"Cause",
			"which",
			"played",
			"angsty",
			"teenager",
			"Jim",
			"Stark"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Solid Snake [accept David or Iroquois Pliskin][10]  This offensive class in Team Fortress 2 wields a Rocket Launcher as his primary weapon. He is fond of crazily waving around his melee weapon, a shovel, and lecturing on Sun Tzu, who he believes invented warfare.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round06.docx | 2 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This protagonist of the Metal Gear series uses a severely overpowered Grenade Launcher as his Final Smash in Super Smash Bros. Brawl. His job as a spy causes him to frequently hide within cardboard boxes.",
		"answers": [
			"Solid",
			"Snake",
			"David",
			"Iroquois",
			"Pliskin",
			"10",
			"This",
			"offensive",
			"class",
			"in",
			"Team",
			"Fortress",
			"2",
			"wields",
			"Rocket",
			"Launcher",
			"as",
			"his",
			"primary",
			"weapon",
			"He",
			"fond",
			"crazily",
			"waving",
			"around",
			"melee",
			"shovel",
			"and",
			"lecturing",
			"Sun",
			"Tzu",
			"who",
			"he",
			"believes",
			"invented",
			"warfare"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Taylor Swift[10]  The band Red fronted by Michael Barnes performs this genre of music. This subgenre of rock features groups like Relient K, Kutless and Skillet, whose 2000 album Ardent Worship contains the track \"Angels Fall Down\".",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round07.docx | 5 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This singer-songwriter released her album Red in 2012, which contains such tracks like \"We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together\". Her 2008 album, Fearless, contains \"Love Story\" and \"You Belong with Me\".",
		"answers": [
			"Taylor",
			"Swift",
			"10",
			"The",
			"band",
			"Red",
			"fronted",
			"by",
			"Michael",
			"Barnes",
			"performs",
			"this",
			"genre",
			"music",
			"This",
			"subgenre",
			"rock",
			"features",
			"groups",
			"Relient",
			"K",
			"Kutless",
			"and",
			"Skillet",
			"whose",
			"2000",
			"album",
			"Ardent",
			"Worship",
			"contains",
			"track",
			"Angels",
			"Fall",
			"Down"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "H.A.M.M.E.R.[10]  In this song, MC Hammer claims you must \"break it down\" since it is \"Hammer time\" and that he is \"dope on the floor and magic on the mic\". He proposes that this song will make listeners thinner since he is \"makin' 'em sweat\".",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round08.docx | 15 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  In the Marvel universe, Norman Osborn reforms S.H.I.E.L.D. into this organization after Tony Stark's security system is compromised by the secret Skrull invasion of Earth. This organization is ultimately dissolved following the failed siege of Asgard.",
		"answers": [
			"H",
			"A",
			"M",
			"E",
			"R",
			"10",
			"In",
			"this",
			"song",
			"MC",
			"Hammer",
			"claims",
			"you",
			"must",
			"break",
			"down",
			"since",
			"time",
			"and",
			"that",
			"he",
			"dope",
			"floor",
			"magic",
			"mic",
			"He",
			"proposes",
			"will",
			"make",
			"listeners",
			"thinner",
			"makin'",
			"'em",
			"sweat"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Dragon Ball Z [or Doragon Boru; accept Dragon Ball suffixed by anything][10]  Hirasawa Yui joins the Light Music club and befriends bassist Mio Akiyama and drummer Tainaka Ritsu in this anime. They later form the band Ho-Kago Tea Time which performs at Sakura High School.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round10.docx | 11 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Goku the Saiyan travels around the world learning martial arts, beating up enemies like Vegeta and Piccolo and searching for the title magical orbs in this 291-episode series.",
		"answers": [
			"Dragon",
			"Ball",
			"Z",
			"Doragon",
			"Boru",
			"suffixed",
			"by",
			"anything",
			"10",
			"Hirasawa",
			"Yui",
			"joins",
			"Light",
			"Music",
			"club",
			"and",
			"befriends",
			"bassist",
			"Mio",
			"Akiyama",
			"drummer",
			"Tainaka",
			"Ritsu",
			"in",
			"this",
			"anime",
			"They",
			"later",
			"form",
			"band",
			"Ho-Kago",
			"Tea",
			"Time",
			"which",
			"performs",
			"at",
			"Sakura",
			"High",
			"School"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Cowboy Bebop [or Kauboi Bibappu][10]  This Joss Whedon-created series centers around the eccentric crew of Serenity, including the pilot Wash, the mercenary Jayne, and the somewhat unstable River, all led by Captain Malcolm Reynolds.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round11.docx | 7 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  An iconic scene from this animated series is the confrontation with Vicious in a church. It follows the bounty hunter Spike Spiegel, who is joined by Edward, Faye Valentine, Jet Black, and the data dog Ein.",
		"answers": [
			"Cowboy",
			"Bebop",
			"Kauboi",
			"Bibappu",
			"10",
			"This",
			"Joss",
			"Whedon-created",
			"series",
			"centers",
			"around",
			"eccentric",
			"crew",
			"Serenity",
			"including",
			"pilot",
			"Wash",
			"mercenary",
			"Jayne",
			"and",
			"somewhat",
			"unstable",
			"River",
			"all",
			"led",
			"by",
			"Captain",
			"Malcolm",
			"Reynolds"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "University of Kentucky Wildcats [or UK][10]  Calipari has been heavily criticized for his recruiting efforts at Kentucky, which focus on players that seek to take advantage of this rule.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round12.docx | 6 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this college basketball team coached by John Calipari.",
		"answers": [
			"University",
			"Kentucky",
			"Wildcats",
			"UK",
			"10",
			"Calipari",
			"has",
			"been",
			"heavily",
			"criticized",
			"for",
			"his",
			"recruiting",
			"efforts",
			"at",
			"which",
			"focus",
			"players",
			"that",
			"seek",
			"to",
			"take",
			"advantage",
			"this",
			"rule"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Michael Phelps[10]  This athlete, at seventeen, was the second-youngest member of the Olympic team. At the Olympics, she swept the backstroke events, and now holds the world record for the women's 100-meter backstroke.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round13.docx | 7 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This man hails from Baltimore, Maryland, and his signature event is the 200 butterfly. He currently holds the world record for most gold medals won at the Olympics.",
		"answers": [
			"Michael",
			"Phelps",
			"10",
			"This",
			"athlete",
			"at",
			"seventeen",
			"was",
			"second-youngest",
			"member",
			"Olympic",
			"team",
			"At",
			"Olympics",
			"she",
			"swept",
			"backstroke",
			"events",
			"and",
			"now",
			"holds",
			"world",
			"record",
			"for",
			"women's",
			"100-meter"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The King's Speech[10]  This actor played the speech therapist Lionel Logue in The King's Speech. He is also known for playing the character of Barbosa in The Pirates of the Caribbean.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2013 | Round15.docx | 9 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This 2010 film starred Colin Firth as King George VI as he works to overcome his stutter with the help of a speech therapist. It won seven British Academy Film Awards, including Best Picture.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"King's",
			"Speech",
			"10",
			"This",
			"actor",
			"played",
			"speech",
			"therapist",
			"Lionel",
			"Logue",
			"in",
			"He",
			"also",
			"known",
			"for",
			"playing",
			"character",
			"Barbosa",
			"Pirates",
			"Caribbean"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Back in Black[10]  Back in Black is a song by this Australian band, famous for other songs such as Shoot to Thrill and Highway to Hell.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round01.docx | 2 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this song, famous for its intro guitar riff, whose singer has \"hit the sack\" and is \"glad\" since he's \"been too long\".",
		"answers": [
			"Back",
			"in",
			"Black",
			"10",
			"song",
			"by",
			"this",
			"Australian",
			"band",
			"famous",
			"for",
			"other",
			"songs",
			"such",
			"as",
			"Shoot",
			"to",
			"Thrill",
			"and",
			"Highway",
			"Hell"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "San Francisco[10]  McDonald's still hasn't re-opened a franchise in this country, due to the low purchasing power of the krona. This nation is governed by the Althing.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round01.docx | 21 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  In 2010, led by Eric Mar, this California city banned the giving of toys along with Happy Meals. It later unrelatedly tried to ban circumcision, but the measure never made it onto the ballot.\n",
		"answers": [
			"San",
			"Francisco",
			"10",
			"McDonald's",
			"still",
			"hasn't",
			"re-opened",
			"franchise",
			"in",
			"this",
			"country",
			"due",
			"to",
			"low",
			"purchasing",
			"power",
			"krona",
			"This",
			"nation",
			"governed",
			"by",
			"Althing"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: Mean Girls[10]  Lindsay Lohan plays both of the twins Hallie and Annie who attempt to bring their divorced mother and father back together in this remake of a 1961 film.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round02.docx | 20 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This teen comedy explained the life of Cady Heron and her adventures with the Regina-led Plastics, who wear pink on Wednesdays.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"Mean",
			"Girls",
			"10",
			"Lindsay",
			"Lohan",
			"plays",
			"both",
			"twins",
			"Hallie",
			"and",
			"Annie",
			"who",
			"attempt",
			"to",
			"bring",
			"their",
			"divorced",
			"mother",
			"father",
			"back",
			"together",
			"in",
			"this",
			"remake",
			"1961",
			"film"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "placekicker[10]  This kicker made the tying and winning field goals for the Patriots in the \"Tuck Rule Game,\" and later made the winning kicks in Super Bowls XXXVI (36) and XXXVIII (38). He now plays for the Colts.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round03.docx | 16 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this position in American football, which is responsible for getting a ball through the uprights to make a field goal or get the extra point after a touchdown.",
		"answers": [
			"placekicker",
			"10",
			"This",
			"kicker",
			"made",
			"tying",
			"and",
			"winning",
			"field",
			"goals",
			"for",
			"Patriots",
			"in",
			"Tuck",
			"Rule",
			"Game",
			"later",
			"kicks",
			"Super",
			"Bowls",
			"XXXVI",
			"36",
			"XXXVIII",
			"38",
			"He",
			"now",
			"plays",
			"Colts"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Key and Peele[10]  Key and Peele have also done multiple skits which mention the teeth of these animals, a talking one of which is voiced by Eddie Murphy in Shrek.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round05.docx | 13 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this show on Comedy Central in which two black comedians perform skits like Dueling Hats, Substitute Teacher, and Pizza Order.",
		"answers": [
			"Key",
			"and",
			"Peele",
			"10",
			"have",
			"also",
			"done",
			"multiple",
			"skits",
			"which",
			"teeth",
			"these",
			"animals",
			"talking",
			"one",
			"voiced",
			"by",
			"Eddie",
			"Murphy",
			"in",
			"Shrek"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: Ferris Bueller (accept either)[10]  At the climax of the film, Cameron causes a red one of these objects owned by his father to go flying out the window and land broken on the ground.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round06.docx | 3 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this character who takes a 'day off' in a John Hughes film, skipping school with his friends Cameron and Sloane.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"Ferris",
			"Bueller",
			"10",
			"At",
			"climax",
			"film",
			"Cameron",
			"causes",
			"red",
			"one",
			"these",
			"objects",
			"owned",
			"by",
			"his",
			"father",
			"to",
			"go",
			"flying",
			"out",
			"window",
			"and",
			"land",
			"broken",
			"ground"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Millenium Falcon[10]  This captain of the Falcon is inseparable from his Wookie friend Chewbacca, the ship's first mate. In the original Star Wars movie, this smuggler played by Harrison Ford shot Greedo first.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round07.docx | 2 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this spaceship, once owned by Lando Calrissian. It was able to make the Kessel run in less than twelve parsecs.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Millenium",
			"Falcon",
			"10",
			"This",
			"captain",
			"inseparable",
			"from",
			"his",
			"Wookie",
			"friend",
			"Chewbacca",
			"ship's",
			"first",
			"mate",
			"In",
			"original",
			"Star",
			"Wars",
			"movie",
			"this",
			"smuggler",
			"played",
			"by",
			"Harrison",
			"Ford",
			"shot",
			"Greedo"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "2 chainz (accept Tauheed Epps or Tity Boi)[10]  2 chainz raps alongside this performer in \"Birthday Song\".  He famously interrupted Taylor Swift at the Video Music Awards and to note that \"Beyonce had one of the best videos of all time\".",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round08.docx | 5 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this rapper, who appeared in \"No Lie\"  along with Drake where he says that he is \"smoking on that gas.\" His current stage name is derived from his trademark jewelry, and he formed Playaz Circle with his friend Dolla Boy.",
		"answers": [
			"2",
			"chainz",
			"Tauheed",
			"Epps",
			"Tity",
			"Boi",
			"10",
			"raps",
			"alongside",
			"this",
			"performer",
			"in",
			"Birthday",
			"Song",
			"He",
			"famously",
			"interrupted",
			"Taylor",
			"Swift",
			"at",
			"Video",
			"Music",
			"Awards",
			"and",
			"to"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "\"Love the Way You Lie\"[10]  This rapper collaborated with Rihanna on \"Love the Way You Lie.\" His latest album, Recovery, features hit singles such as \"Not Afraid,\" and one of his most successful albums was 1999's The Slim Shady LP.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round09.docx | 21 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this song in which the main artist claims that their crazy relationship is \"what happens when a tornado meets a volcano,\" but never seems to tell the truth.",
		"answers": [
			"Love",
			"Way",
			"You",
			"Lie",
			"10",
			"This",
			"rapper",
			"collaborated",
			"with",
			"Rihanna",
			"His",
			"latest",
			"album",
			"Recovery",
			"features",
			"hit",
			"singles",
			"such",
			"as"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: Minecraft[10]  This battle arena game, developed by Riot Games, features a spawn point called the \"spawning pool\" and includes such features as Nexuses and Turrets.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round10.docx | 2 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This indie game developed by Mojang Inc. was created by Markus Persson, also known as Notch. It features one by one meter blocks to form the gameplay world.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"Minecraft",
			"10",
			"This",
			"battle",
			"arena",
			"game",
			"developed",
			"by",
			"Riot",
			"Games",
			"features",
			"spawn",
			"point",
			"called",
			"spawning",
			"pool",
			"and",
			"includes",
			"such",
			"as",
			"Nexuses",
			"Turrets"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Citizen Kane (or Charles Foster Kane)[10]  Citizen Kane was directed by this man, who also played the title role. He also famously read The War of the Worlds on the radio, inciting a small panic.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round11.docx | 3 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this media magnate, the title character of the film in which he appears, who dies while dropping a snowglobe and saying the word \"Rosebud.\"",
		"answers": [
			"Citizen",
			"Kane",
			"Charles",
			"Foster",
			"10",
			"was",
			"directed",
			"by",
			"this",
			"man",
			"who",
			"also",
			"played",
			"title",
			"role",
			"He",
			"famously",
			"read",
			"The",
			"War",
			"Worlds",
			"radio",
			"inciting",
			"small",
			"panic"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Walking Dead[10]  This network broadcasts The Walking Dead, Mad Men, and Breaking Bad.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round11.docx | 19 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Name this show in which Rick Grimes leads a group on the run from zombies in northern Georgia.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Walking",
			"Dead",
			"10",
			"This",
			"network",
			"broadcasts",
			"Mad",
			"Men",
			"and",
			"Breaking",
			"Bad"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: Downton Abbey[10]  This third cousin of the Earl becomes the heir presumptive to the estate after the deaths of the other heirs on the RMS Titanic. He later marries Mary.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round12.docx | 5 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This television series centers around the title fictional estate set in Yorkshire, England and focuses on the aristocratic Crawley family and their servants.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"Downton",
			"Abbey",
			"10",
			"This",
			"third",
			"cousin",
			"Earl",
			"becomes",
			"heir",
			"presumptive",
			"to",
			"estate",
			"after",
			"deaths",
			"other",
			"heirs",
			"RMS",
			"Titanic",
			"He",
			"later",
			"marries",
			"Mary"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic[10]  This cyan-colored pegasus pony is known for her daring flight stunts and seeks to join an elite group of pony flyers called the \"Wonderbolts\". She is the only pony known to have successfully completed a \"sonic rainboom.\"",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round13.docx | 5 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  Identify this television series, the first episode of which sees Twilight Sparkle and her friends unite the Elements of Harmony to save Equestria from Nightmare Moon.",
		"answers": [
			"My",
			"Little",
			"Pony:",
			"Friendship",
			"Magic",
			"10",
			"This",
			"cyan-colored",
			"pegasus",
			"pony",
			"known",
			"for",
			"her",
			"daring",
			"flight",
			"stunts",
			"and",
			"seeks",
			"to",
			"join",
			"an",
			"elite",
			"group",
			"flyers",
			"called",
			"Wonderbolts",
			"She",
			"only",
			"have",
			"successfully",
			"completed",
			"sonic",
			"rainboom"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Stephen Colbert[10]  Colbert's best friend for six months was this man, who was part of the cast of SNL before getting his own late-night show on NBC. The house band for his show is The Roots.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round14.docx | 9 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This man got his start on the Daily Show, and now hosts his own namesake Report [\"ruh-PORE\"]on Comedy Central, a parody of Fox News opinion shows.",
		"answers": [
			"Stephen",
			"Colbert",
			"10",
			"Colbert's",
			"best",
			"friend",
			"for",
			"six",
			"months",
			"was",
			"this",
			"man",
			"who",
			"part",
			"cast",
			"SNL",
			"getting",
			"his",
			"own",
			"late-night",
			"show",
			"NBC",
			"The",
			"house",
			"band",
			"Roots"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: The Princess Bride[10]  This Reiner film focuses on the murder of PFC William Santiago under a \"code red\" ordered by Colonel Jessep, who informs Kaffee that he \"can't handle the truth.\"",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round15.docx | 2 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  \"Wuv, twoo wuv\" is the subject of this comedic film in which Wesley works with Inigo Montoya to rescue Buttercup from Prince Humperdink.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"The",
			"Princess",
			"Bride",
			"10",
			"This",
			"Reiner",
			"film",
			"focuses",
			"murder",
			"PFC",
			"William",
			"Santiago",
			"under",
			"code",
			"red",
			"ordered",
			"by",
			"Colonel",
			"Jessep",
			"who",
			"informs",
			"Kaffee",
			"that",
			"he",
			"can't",
			"handle",
			"truth"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Answer: A Game of Thrones[10]  Lord Eddard Stark is stabbed non-fatally by this Lord Commander of the Kingsguard, the eldest son of Tywin and incestuous lover of Cersei.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "LIST (Ladue Invitational Spring Tournament) |2012 | LISTIII_Round16.docx | 9 | Trash |  | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question:  [10]  This first novel in \"A Song of Ice and Fire\" details the reign and death of King Robert I Baratheon.",
		"answers": [
			"Answer:",
			"A",
			"Game",
			"Thrones",
			"10",
			"Lord",
			"Eddard",
			"Stark",
			"stabbed",
			"non-fatally",
			"by",
			"this",
			"Commander",
			"Kingsguard",
			"eldest",
			"son",
			"Tywin",
			"and",
			"incestuous",
			"lover",
			"Cersei"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Oliver Stanley \"Olly\" Murs[10] Murs came in second on 6th season of this show's British version. The boy band One Direction was formed on  this talent-search show, created by Simon Cowell years after American Idol.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl  |2012 | 1 | 5 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: In one song by this musician, he declares \"I swear you're giving me a heart attack\" right before singing the title  word. For 10 points each: [10] Name this singer whose song \"Troublemaker\" features Flo Rida. His singles \"Heart Skips a Beat\" and \"Dance  with Me Tonight\" also topped the British charts.",
		"answers": [
			"Oliver",
			"Stanley",
			"Olly",
			"Murs",
			"10",
			"came",
			"in",
			"second",
			"6th",
			"season",
			"this",
			"show's",
			"British",
			"version",
			"The",
			"boy",
			"band",
			"One",
			"Direction",
			"was",
			"formed",
			"talent-search",
			"show",
			"created",
			"by",
			"Simon",
			"Cowell",
			"years",
			"after",
			"American",
			"Idol"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Oliver Stanley \"Olly\" Murs[10] Murs came in second on 6th season of this show's British version. The boy band One Direction was formed on  this talent-search show, created by Simon Cowell years after American Idol.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl  |2012 | 1 | 5 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: In one song by this musician, he declares \"I swear you're giving me a heart attack\" right before singing the title  word. For 10 points each: [10] Name this singer whose song \"Troublemaker\" features Flo Rida. His singles \"Heart Skips a Beat\" and \"Dance  with Me Tonight\" also topped the British charts.",
		"answers": [
			"Oliver",
			"Stanley",
			"Olly",
			"Murs",
			"10",
			"came",
			"in",
			"second",
			"6th",
			"season",
			"this",
			"show's",
			"British",
			"version",
			"The",
			"boy",
			"band",
			"One",
			"Direction",
			"was",
			"formed",
			"talent-search",
			"show",
			"created",
			"by",
			"Simon",
			"Cowell",
			"years",
			"after",
			"American",
			"Idol"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Smashing Pumpkins[10] One former saxophone player for this band was Derek Kwan. This Californian alternative rock band is known  almost entirely for their 2004 single \"The Reason,\" which begins with the line \"I'm not a perfect person.\"",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2012 | 2 | 10 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Name some related bands, for 10 points each: [10] This band fronted by Billy Corgan formerly had rhythm guitarist James Iha. Their albums include Siamese  Dream and Mellon Collie and the Infinite Sadness. After reforming in 2005, they released the album Zeitgeist.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Smashing",
			"Pumpkins",
			"10",
			"One",
			"former",
			"saxophone",
			"player",
			"for",
			"this",
			"band",
			"was",
			"Derek",
			"Kwan",
			"This",
			"Californian",
			"alternative",
			"rock",
			"known",
			"almost",
			"entirely",
			"their",
			"2004",
			"single",
			"Reason",
			"which",
			"begins",
			"with",
			"line",
			"I'm"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Mewtwo[10] This Pokémon was originally going to be the mascot of the series, but that role was ultimately taken by  Pikachu. It evolves using a Moon Stone into Clefable.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2012 | 3 | 9 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: So you wanna be a master of Pokémon? Then name some. For 10 points each: [10] This Pokémon, number 150, comes earlier in the Pokédex than the Pokémon it was supposedly a clone of.",
		"answers": [
			"Mewtwo",
			"10",
			"This",
			"Pokémon",
			"was",
			"originally",
			"going",
			"to",
			"be",
			"mascot",
			"series",
			"but",
			"that",
			"role",
			"ultimately",
			"taken",
			"by",
			"Pikachu",
			"It",
			"evolves",
			"using",
			"Moon",
			"Stone",
			"into",
			"Clefable"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Seventh Seal [or Det Sjunde Inseglet][10] The Seventh Seal [or Det Sjunde Inseglet]",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2012 | 5 | 9 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: ends with a danse macabre witnessed by Jof, an actor. For 10 points each: [10] Name this film in which Antonius Block, a crusader who returned to a plague-ravaged Sweden, plays chess against Death.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Seventh",
			"Seal",
			"Det",
			"Sjunde",
			"Inseglet",
			"10"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Sopranos[10] This semi-fictional comedy show involves mostly improvised dialogue between characters, and stars Larry David as himself.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "Prison Bowl |2012 | 5 | 10 | Trash | American | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: Name some HBO shows, for 10 points each: [10] The pilot of this show involves the protagonist meeting with therapist Jennifer Melfi. This most-successful show ever focuses on Tony, a Mafia boss, and his relationship with his work and his family, which the show is named for. ",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Sopranos",
			"10",
			"This",
			"semi-fictional",
			"comedy",
			"show",
			"involves",
			"mostly",
			"improvised",
			"dialogue",
			"between",
			"characters",
			"and",
			"stars",
			"Larry",
			"David",
			"as",
			"himself"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Psych[10] In the series finale of season 3 of Psych, fake psychic Shawn Spencer is challenged by Mr. Yang, a serial killer based on this famous Bay Area serial killer who was active in 60's and 70's California.  A movie based on this killer was released in 2007.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BHSAT |2011 | 1 | 12 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, answer these seemingly unrelated questions: [10] Starring Dulé Hill and James Roday, the main protagonist of this television show is obsessed with pineapples. The actors playing a pair of detectives for the Santa Barbara police each starred in made-for-TV movies: Model Behavior and The Luck of the Irish.",
		"answers": [
			"Psych",
			"10",
			"In",
			"series",
			"finale",
			"season",
			"3",
			"fake",
			"psychic",
			"Shawn",
			"Spencer",
			"challenged",
			"by",
			"Mr",
			"Yang",
			"serial",
			"killer",
			"based",
			"this",
			"famous",
			"Bay",
			"Area",
			"who",
			"was",
			"active",
			"in",
			"60's",
			"and",
			"70's",
			"California",
			"A",
			"movie",
			"released",
			"2007"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "Psych[10] In the series finale of season 3 of Psych, fake psychic Shawn Spencer is challenged by Mr. Yang, a serial killer based on this famous Bay Area serial killer who was active in 60's and 70's California.  A movie based on this killer was released in 2007.",
		"prompts": [],
		"heading": "BHSAT |2011 | 1 | 12 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: For 10 points each, answer these seemingly unrelated questions: [10] Starring Dulé Hill and James Roday, the main protagonist of this television show is obsessed with pineapples. The actors playing a pair of detectives for the Santa Barbara police each starred in made-for-TV movies: Model Behavior and The Luck of the Irish.",
		"answers": [
			"Psych",
			"10",
			"In",
			"series",
			"finale",
			"season",
			"3",
			"fake",
			"psychic",
			"Shawn",
			"Spencer",
			"challenged",
			"by",
			"Mr",
			"Yang",
			"serial",
			"killer",
			"based",
			"this",
			"famous",
			"Bay",
			"Area",
			"who",
			"was",
			"active",
			"in",
			"60's",
			"and",
			"70's",
			"California",
			"A",
			"movie",
			"released",
			"2007"
		]
	},
	{
		"answerText": "The Man Your Man Could Smell Like [prompt \"Isaiah Mustafa;\" prompt answers such as \"Old Spice guy,\" though don't let teams know you can prompt them unless you do prompt this][10]  The Man Your Man Could Smell Like is in ads for this deodorant brand which produces Red Zone body spray. Its other campaigns include \"Experience is Everything.\"",
		"prompts": [
			"Isaiah",
			"Mustafa"
		],
		"heading": "BHSAT |2011 | 2 | 12 | Trash | None | HS",
		"subject": "Trash",
		"level": "HS",
		"question": "Question: In one parody of this figure, Grover of Sesame Street teaches children how to use the word \"on,\" and a seashell in his hand opens up to \"tickets to that thing you love,\" which melt into diamonds. For 10 points each: [10] Name this African-American figure first seen in a shower saying \"Look at your man, now back to me\" and later seen on a horse.",
		"answers": [
			"The",
			"Man",
			"Your",
			"Could",
			"Smell",
			"Like"
		]
	}
]